A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Press Office, Series 25 FA368
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Public Relations File, 1; 59 Cubic Feet
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 302)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 303)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 304)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 305)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 306)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 307)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 308)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 309)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 310)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 311)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 312)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 313)
  - July 12, 1963 - December 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 314)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 315)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 316)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 317)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 318)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 319)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 320)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 321)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 322)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 323)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 324)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 325)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 326)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 327)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 328)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 329)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 330)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 331)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 332)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 333)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 334)
  - January 1, 1964 - March 31, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 336)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 337)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 338)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 339)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 340)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 341)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 342)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 343)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 344)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 345)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 346)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 347)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 348)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 349)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 350)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 351)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 352)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 353)
  - April 1, 1964 - December 29, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 354)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 355)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 356)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 357)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 358)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 359)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 360)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 361)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 362)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 363)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 364)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 365)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 366)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 367)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 368)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 369)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 370)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 371)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 372)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 373)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 374)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 375)
  - January 1, 1965 - June 30, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 376)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 377)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 378)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 379)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 380)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 381)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 382)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 383)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 384)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 385)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 386)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 387)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 388)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 389)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 390)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 391)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 392)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 393)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 394)
  - July 16, 1965 - May 17, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 395)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 396)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 397)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 398)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 399)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 400)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 401)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 402)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 403)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 404)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 405)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 406)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 407)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 408)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 409)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 410)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 411)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 412)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 413)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 414)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 415)
  - June 2, 1966 - December 30, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 416)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 417)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 418)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 419)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 420)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 421)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 422)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 423)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 424)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 425)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 426)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 427)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 428)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 429)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 430)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 431)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 432)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 433)
  - January 3, 1967 - May 12, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 434)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 435)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 436)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 437)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 438)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 439)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 440)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 441)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 442)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 443)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 444)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 445)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 446)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 447)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 448)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 449)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 450)
  - May 15, 1967 - November 3, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 451)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 452)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 453)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 454)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 455)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 456)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 457)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 458)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 459)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 460)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 461)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 462)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 463)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 464)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 465)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 466)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 467)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 468)
  - November 7, 1967 - January 9, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 469)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 470)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 471)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 472)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 473)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 474)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 475)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 476)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 477)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 478)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 479)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 480)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 481)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 482)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 483)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 484)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 485)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 486)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 487)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 488)
  - January 10, 1968 - March 20, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 489)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 490)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 491)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 492)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 493)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 494)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 495)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 496)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 497)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 498)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 499)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 500)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 501)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 502)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 503)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 504)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 505)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 506)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 507)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 508)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 509)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 510)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 511)
  - March 22, 1968 - May 21, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 512)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 513)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 514)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 515)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 516)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 517)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 518)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 519)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 520)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 521)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 522)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 523)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 524)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 525)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 526)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 527)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 528)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 529)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 530)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 531)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 532)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 533)
  - May 22, 1968 - July 8, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 534)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 535)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 536)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 537)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 538)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 539)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 540)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 541)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 542)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 543)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 544)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 545)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 546)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 547)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 548)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 549)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 550)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 551)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 552)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 553)
  - July 9, 1968 - October 31, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 554)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 555)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 556)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 557)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 558)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 559)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 560)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 561)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 562)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 563)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 564)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 565)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 566)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 567)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 568)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 569)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 570)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 571)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 572)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 573)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 574)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 575)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 576)
  - November 1, 1968 - January 24, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 577)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 578)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 579)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 580)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 581)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 582)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 583)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 584)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 585)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 586)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 587)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 588)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 589)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 590)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 591)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 592)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 593)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 594)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 595)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 596)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 597)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 598)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 599)
  - January 24, 1969 - February 6, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 600)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 601)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 602)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 603)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 604)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 605)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 606)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 607)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 608)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 609)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 610)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 611)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 612)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 613)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 614)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 615)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 616)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 617)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 618)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 619)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 620)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 621)
  - February 6, 1969 - March 7, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 622)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 623)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 624)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 625)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 626)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 627)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 628)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 629)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 630)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 631)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 632)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 633)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 634)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 635)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 636)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 637)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 638)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 639)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 640)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 641)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 642)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 643)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 644)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 645)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 646)
  - March 9, 1969 - June 10, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 647)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 648)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 649)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 650)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 651)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 652)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 653)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 654)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 655)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 656)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 657)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 658)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 659)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 660)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 661)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 662)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 663)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 664)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 665)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 666)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 667)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 668)
  - June 11, 1969 - October 2, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 669)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 670)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 671)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 672)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 673)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 674)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 675)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 676)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 677)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 678)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 679)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 680)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 681)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 682)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 683)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 684)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 685)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 686)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 687)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 688)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 689)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 690)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 691)
  - October 3, 1969 - November 23, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 692)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 693)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 694)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 695)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 696)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 697)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 698)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 699)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 700)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 701)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 702)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 703)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 704)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 705)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 706)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 707)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 708)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 709)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 710)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 711)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 712)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 713)